JESSIE COLEMAN

Decatur GA · (915) 831 9109 Jessiecoleman928@gmail.com

Upcoming paid intern at Publicis Sapient for Summer 2023. Third year student at Emory University. Experienced with working under fast-paced, Agile environment, as well as OOP programming, website design, app design, and game development.

EXPERIENCE

AUG 2022 - PRESENT

EMORY COMPUTER SCIENCE LAB STAFF

My responsibilities include tutoring computer science students, computer repair, and computer maintenance.

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

BEST BUY COMPUTER REPAIR

My job was to diagnose and fix software/hardware problems with clients' computers, as well as smartphones and tablets.

EDUCATION

MAY 2019

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, FRANKLIN HIGH SCHOOL

JUNE 2020-PRESENT

COMPUTER SCIENCE, EMORY UNIVERSITY

SKILLS

- Java/C#/C
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript

- Python/Lua
- Unity/Android Studio/Arduino

PROJECTS

- Created online multiplayer tank game https://sacredstudios.itch.io/chidi-tanks-03-alpha
- Created visualization of A* pathfinding algorithm using Arduino.
- Created website using CSS/JavaScript/HTML.
- Created map/sprites for 2D game with Unity
- Created simple clicker game using Lua.
- Created animated poster using Android Studio.